<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mines Sweeper</string>

    <string name="quitTitle">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="quitTxt">Are you sure you want to leave the game?</string>
    <string name="exitTitle">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="exitTxt">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="ad">Ad enabled</string>
    <string name="sign_in_failed">Failed to sign in. Please check your network connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="app_misconfigured">The application is incorrectly configured. Check that the package name and signing certificate match the client ID created in Developer Console. Also, if the application is not yet published, check that the account you are trying to sign in with is listed as a tester account. See logs for more information.</string>
    <string name="license_failed">License check failed.</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">Unknown error.</string>

    <string name="bombs_flag_toast">Hai già messo %1$d bandiere!</string>
    <string name="share_extra_subject">Download this new Game!</string>
    <string name="shate_extra_text">Hi, download this new Game at: https://play.google.com/store/apps?hl=it</string>
    <string name="share_chooser_text">Share this Game!</string>

    <string name="rules_description">The player is initially presented with a grid of undifferentiated squares.
        \nSome randomly selected squares, unknown to the player, are designated to contain mines.
        \n\nThe game is played by revealing squares of the grid by clicking each square. If a square containing a mine is revealed,
        the player loses the game. If no mine is revealed, a digit is instead displayed in the square, indicating how many adjacent
        squares contain mines; if no mines are adjacent, the square becomes blank, and all adjacent squares will be recursively revealed.
        \n\nThe player uses this information to deduce the contents of other squares, and may either safely reveal each square or
        mark the square as containing a mine.</string>
    <string name="howToPlay">How To Play?</string>
</resources>
